war2glory.co.uk 2014-11-21

# WAR2GLORY: Privacy Policy

As of: 1st of August 2013

1\. Collection of data

GameSpree GmbH & Co. KG (hereinafter "GameSpree") (responsible party in terms of data privacy law), collects, processes and uses personal data of visitors to the internet pages of GameSpree in order to fulfill contractual obligations toward its partners and visitors (hereinafter “User”).

a. Log files

GameSpree automatically collects certain data which is saved in log files. This data includes IP addresses, browser information, internet service providers, referring sites, operating systems in use, date and time stamps and clickstream data. This data does not contain any personal user information and GameSpree uses it for trend analysis, for site administration, to track the user's navigation of the website as well as to gather demographic data on our user community. The data collected automatically is not linked with personal data.

b. Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is saved on the user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are also used on the internet pages of GameSpree. GameSpree does not link any information in the cookies with personal user data that GameSpree may collect, process and use for other purposes. We use both session cookies and permanent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A permanent cookie is saved on your hard disk for a longer period of time. You can reject cookies or delete permanent cookies by following the instructions in the help function of your browser.

GameSpree uses temporary cookies to make navigating our site with your browser easier, to determine which users have come to our internet pages from the sites of our business partners and to facilitate the proper authentication of the user in a user session. Permanent cookies are used by GameSpree to recall user data so the user can save time in filling out forms and/or when returning to our website. GameSpree also uses permanent cookies to determine whether users have already visited the internet pages of GameSpree and, if so, for what purpose.

The user can still access the information on the internet pages of GameSpree even if he/she rejects cookies.

c. Contract data

The collection, processing and use of all personal user data is conducted within the framework of initiating, implementing or terminating contractual legal relationships between GameSpree and its users on the basis of the German Data Protection Act (Bundesdatenschutzgesetzes; BDSG) and the German Broadcast Media Act (Telemediengesetzes; TMG) as well as other compulsory regulations or with the consent of those concerned.

2\. User rights

All natural persons whose personal data has been collected, processed or used are entitled at any time to information regarding the personal data that has been recorded, the purpose of its recording as well as the source and recipient of the data when applicable. The provision of this information is free of charge for those concerned. Rights of rectification, deletion or blocking (Art. 35 BDSG) shall remain unaffected. In order to exercise your right to the provision of information, rectification, deletion or blocking of personal data please apply in writing to:

GameSpree GmbH & Co. KG  
Glogauer Strasse 6  
10999 Berlin  
Germany  
[dataprotection[at]war2glory.com](http://dataprotection@war2glory.com/ "Opens window for sending email")

Unfortunately we are unable to respond to requests submitted by phone as the identity of the person requesting information cannot be verified. Email requests are ONLY accepted when they originate from the email address associated with the users account. All requests relating to other accounts or from other email addresses will not be processed.

3\. Advertising and Transfer to third parties

Should the user have supplied GameSpree with their Email Address as part of their ongoing customer relationship, GameSpree may send the user information about the company itself or regarding services similar to those already used by the user as part of their GameSpree services. GameSpree also has the right to supply the user with information regarding subsidiaries of GameSpree and their products and services via email. The user may withdraw their consent to such contact from GameSpree at any time in writing (i.e. Email) without incurring any extra costs other than for the communication of the withdrawal of consent. The user will be offered a possibility to withdraw their consent regarding future communication in every communication sent from GameSpree.  
The transfer of personal user data to third parties is only conducted with the express consent of those concerned. Exempted from this are the service partners of GameSpree, inasmuch as doing so is necessary to fulfill contractual agreements with the user. A transfer of your data may also in some cases become necessary to fulfill the legal obligations of GameSpree. In particular, GameSpree will not transfer your data to third parties for the purpose of advertising offers from others.

Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics. This is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. ?Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. On behalf of the website provider Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider.Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>.  
Further information concerning the terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html> or at <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html>. Please note that on this website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by “gat._anonymizeIp();” to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking).

Google AdWords

We furthermore use data from Google Analytics to statistically analyse data from AdWords and the Double-Click Cookie. Should you wish to prevent this, you may deactivate this via the Ad Setting Manager (<http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en>).

Data usage in connection with Social Networks

On our websites there are multiple references to so-called „Social Networks“. Of particular note is the Social Media Site „Facebook.com“. We reserve the right to extend data usage to include other social networks and to make relevant changes to this Privacy Policy in light of this. References to Social Networks and / or their services (e.g. “Facebook – Connect”, or other Social Plugins from Facebook) will be duly marked (for example by the Facebook logo).

General Information about „Social Plugins“ from Facebook 

Our internet presences use Social Plugins of the Social Network Facebook.com. The responsible operator of which in Europe is Facebook Ireland Ltd., Hanover Reach, 5 - 7 Hanover Quay, Dublin 2, Ireland. Furthermore this Social Network is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The relevant Plugins are recognizable via the Facebook logo (a white ‘f’ on a blue tile or a “thumbs-up” symbol). They may also be marked with the addition “Facebook Social Plugin” (a list of Social Plugins operated by Facebook can be found here: <http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins>).

Through the use of Social Plugins on our website your browser will be connected with the technical systems (servers) of the applicable operator (e.g. Facebook). The content of these Social Plugins will be transmitted directly from the applicable operator to your browser and displayed directly by the operator in the applicable website. Through the use of and via such a Social Plugin information will be sent to the operator regarding your use of the Social Plugin via our webpage. Should you be logged in to the Social Network operator service at this time the operator may connect the use of our website with your relevant account and may furthermore use this connection and analyze the relevant data transmitted within legal means. As a consequence of the use of a Social Plugin (such as for example the clicking of a „Like“ button) data will be transmitted and stored by the relevant operator of the Social Network.

Information on „Facebook Connect“

To Login to our websites we offer multiple alternatives to users. One of these is through the use of Facebook Connect. Should you chose to use Facebook Connect to login to our websites Facebook will, after receiving confirmation of your consent, transmit data to us. With the transmission of this data a new user account on our website will be created in certain circumstances. For the time in which you use our services transmission of data will take place. Should you wish to prevent the transmission of data described you must not be logged in to the relevant operator (e.g. Facebook) prior to visiting our websites and avoid logging in while using them. For further information on the type of, scope and purpose of data storage, handling and usage by the relevant Social Network operator please consult the regularly updated Terms of Service and Privacy Policy of the relevant operator.

Privacy policy for the use of the Facebook „Like“ Button

Should you chose to click the Facebook „Like“ button during a visit to one of our websites you may link to the contents of our websites via your Facebook profile. Outside of our control Facebook may associate the visiting of our websites and the click of the „Like“ button signifying content you find likeable with your Facebook User Account. We advise you that as the operator of our website we do not have any control over the data transmitted in such an event and have no influence on how Facebook may use such data. The purpose and scope of data collection and their further use and handling by Facebook, as well as your rights and any settings controlling the data Facebook collects can only be seen in the Privacy Policy of Facebook:  <http://facebook.com/about/privacy>.

4\. GameSpree Security measures

GameSpree has implemented all the technical and organisational requirements required in terms of Art. 9 of the German Data Protection Act (BDSG) to ensure that all recorded, administered or used data are protected from accidental or intentional changes or unauthorised access.

5\. Privacy policy modifications

GameSpree will announce any changes made to this privacy policy on its website.

6\. Contact Details

The data protection officer at GameSpree can be reached for inquiries or other comments and requests at:

GameSpree GmbH & Co. KG  
Glogauer Strasse 6  
10999 Berlin  
Germany

E-Mail: [dataprotection[at]war2glory.com](http://dataprotection@war2glory.com/ "Opens window for sending email")
